http://www.bannerengineering.com/content/banner/us/en/company/privacy-policy.html

Machine Safety Software
In-Series Diagnostics (ISD)
Learn More
Imager-Based Barcode Readers (1D, 2D)
Laser Barcode Scanners (1D)
Intrinsic Safety
In-Series Diagnostics (ISD)
Further Expand Your ISD System with New ISD Connect
Improved Delivery Provides Easy Access to Cloud Data Services
Predictive Maintenance
Overall Equipment Effectiveness (OEE)
Tank Level Monitoring
Factory Communication
Leading Edge Detection
IO-Link
Vibration Monitoring a Main Air Handler [Success Story]
Greater China
Chinese (Simplified)
Chinese (Traditional)
Saved for Session
The document will be available in your library until the end of your session. To save permanently, please create an account.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of Banner Engineering Corp. Your use of www.bannerengineering.com (the "Site") indicates your acceptance of the provisions in this Privacy Policy.
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE
Banner may use various methods to collect certain kinds of information that is disclosed through your use of the Site, including:
Cookies
Web beacons
Referrers
IP addresses
System information
Future technologies and methods
We treat all personal information that we collect with the same confidentiality, no matter how it is collected.
Cookies
A "cookie" is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored it on your computer system. It can help provide you with a tailored user experience, to understand your preferences and to personalize the content you see. Some the Site's pages may use cookies. Banner does not require that you accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive cookies, and to block them.
Cookie
Purpose
Details
My Account
Allows us to determine that you are registered, to login, and to access secure areas of the site.
Unless you check the remember me box, they will expire at the end of the session.
Location
This cookie allows us to recommend distributors and factory representatives in our Where to Buy section.
These are session cookies, which are deleted when you close your browser.
Shopping Cart
If you enter the shopping cart section of the website, a cookie is used to save your cart items and your options. These are remembered from page to page.
These are session cookies, which are deleted when you close your browser.
Google Analytics
These are cookies set by Google. Their privacy policy applies.
These are persistent cookies
Google Retargeting
These are cookies set by Google for advertising purposes. Their privacy policy applies.
These are persistent cookies
Personalization purposes
These cookies allow us to more specifically serve your needs by tailoring content to your specific interests on the website.
These are persistent cookies
Keep track of facets
These cookies allow us to remember what facets you have selected. These are remembered from page to page.
These are session cookies, which are deleted when you close your browser.
Compare function
These cookies allow us to remember that you’ve selected products to compare. These are remembered from page to page.
These are session cookies, which are deleted when you close your browser.
Changing Cookie Preferences
You can change your cookie preference to accept or decline cookies at any time.
Cookies
You previously declined cookies. Update preferences to accept cookies?
You previously accepted cookies. Update preferences to decline cookies?
Please confirm that you would like to accept cookies.
No Change
Accept Cookies
Decline Cookies
No Change
Decline Cookies
Accept Cookies
Web Beacons
Web beacons are images that can be placed in web pages and some forms of email. Web beacons can be used to deliver cookies and to collect information about your use of the Site. For example, we may use web beacons to count the number of your visits to the Site.
Referrers
A "referrer" is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL from which you come to the Site. Referrers are automatically collected by Banner web servers. They are used by Banner to identify the websites referring traffic to the Site, and to present appropriate content to the Site's users. Referrer information may be used by Banner to identify general trends and traffic patterns. For example, Banner may use referrer information to identify the information on the Site that is viewed by individuals referred by certain websites.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. They are automatically collected by Banner web servers.
System Information
System information Banner collects might include, among other things, the type of web browser being used. This information is sent automatically by your web browser when you are connected to the Site and is used by Banner only for identify broad demographic statistics and general trends and traffic patterns.
Account and Purchase Information
When you register to establish an account with Banner or complete form to receive additional information from Banner, you provide certain information. We use that information for the sole purpose of maintaining your account and communicating with you about Banner products and your purchases. When you purchase Banner products you provide credit card and other additional information. We use that information for the sole purpose of facilitating your purchase.
Offline Collection
At times we might collect information from you through means other than the Site. For example, if you call to place on order or to check on the status of an order, we will collect telephone numbers or other information needed to communicate with you.
Banner Mobile Library Application
Except for certain location information and information about the portions of the Banner website accessed with the Banner Mobile Library Application, Banner does not collect any more information from the Banner Mobile Library Application than it does through the Site. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, Banner does not disclose any of that other information.
Future Technologies and Methods
As technologies change, we may collect information in different ways. However, we will continue to treat all personal information that we collect in the same manner, unless we modify this Privacy Policy to provide notice of any change.
2. INFORMATION BANNER SHARES WITH OTHERS
At times, Banner must disclose information about Banner customers to Banner business partners. For example, Banner might need to disclose certain information to Banner contractors, so that they may perform services for us. In particular, we must provide some information to others in order to facilitate your purchases of Banner products.
Banner requires such contractors and business partners to keep your information confidential. Banner may disclose personal information to such contractors and business partners without additional notice.
Banner may also disclose to others the information collected by Banner regarding your access and use of the Site, provided that it is that is de-identified and aggregated with other data to you. This information might include referrer information and the other information that we collect through the Site.
3. CONTACT US
Please contact us with any Privacy Policy questions or comments you may have.
4. CHANGES TO BANNER PRIVACY POLICY
Banner's use of the information that Banner collects about you is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is provided or collected. However, Banner may change this Privacy Policy. You should check the Site for changes to the Banner Privacy Policy.
5. GOVERNING LAW
This Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Minnesota, United States of America. All controversies and claims arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy will be settled by arbitration in Minneapolis, Minnesota administered by the American Arbitration Association under your Commercial Arbitration Rules. The arbitration will be conducted in the English language. Judgment on any award rendered by the arbitrator(s) may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof.
×
